



CONTACT INFORMATION

Phone Number: 438-509-4237 Email: davidholcer@gmail.com Github: <u>github.com/davidholcer</u> LinkedIn: @david-holcer Website: <u>david.holcer.github.io</u>



SUMMARY:

David is entering his fourth year at McGill University pursuing a B.Sc. in Mathematics and Computer Science.

David has over 3 years experience tutoring mathematics and 3 years experience as a camp counsellor. Within these roles David has strengthened his problem solving abilities and become an effective team leader.

I am currently seeking employment to consolidate new skills and to apply my current experience within a team setting.

EDUCATION:



Bachelor of Science (2019-2024)

Pursuing a joint degree in Mathematics and Computer Science.

CGPA: 3.78

McGill Artificial Intelligence Society Bootcamp Course Graduate:

(Sept. 2019 - Nov. 2019)

Simon Fraser University Research Intern

Vancouver, BC

(June 2017 - Sept. 2017)

Novel Genomics Data Clustering & Compression Method

HOBBIES:

- Cooking
- Climbing
- Chess
- Creative Coding

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS:

- French Professional Working Proficiency
- English and Spanish Native Speaker
- Graphic Design
- Python, Java/JS, Processing, Mathematica, Bash

WORK EXPERIENCE:

McGill University (Montreal, QC)

Mathematics Tutor (Jan. 2020 - May 2022)

- Guided numerous students to mastery in mathematics courses, leading them to excel in their exams through one-on-one sessions.
- Courses included: Calculus 1,2,3; Linear Algebra

Camp Miriam (Gabriola Island, BC)

Summer Camp Counselor (June - Aug. 2019, 2020, 2021)

- Created and facilitated interactive educational activities for youth aged 9-16.
- Led and communicated within a team of 4-5 people, directly overseeing the health, safety, and well-being of 10+ campers.
- Responded rapidly and calmly in high pressure situations finding creative solutions to solve difficult problems.
- Led informal educational discussions about pressing modern-day societal issues.

Geek Education (Remote)

Online Teacher (June 2020 - Oct. 2020)

Taught the Java AP Curriculum to a cohort of 14-year-old students.

- Created challenging coding examples and projects to work through with students.
- Presented course material in an engaging way adapting to each student's needs and answering all questions thoroughly.